A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Finance, 1992; 1994; 2000-2018 (bulk 2013-2017)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Decision Briefs, 2014-2017., Extent: 2 boxes (2.0 cu. ft.). (Box 8-9)
  - 2014 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 2014 Oct (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 2014 Sept (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 2014 Aug (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 2014 June-July (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 2014 Apr-May (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 2014 Jan-Mar (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Series IV. Joint Money Committee Meetings Files, 2005; 2007-2014; 2016-2017., Extent: 4 boxes (2.05 cu. ft.). (Box 10-12; 23)
  Series IV. Joint Money Committee Meetings Files, 2005; 2007-2014; 2016-2017, created and maintained by Secretary of Finance Ric Brown, during multiple gubernatorial administrations, is housed in 4 boxes. This series contains presentations to the Joint Money Committee (House Appropriation and Senate Finance) and supporting documentation (correspondence, speeches, meeting notes and reports). Subjects include the state budget, revenue reports, tax impact assessments, and fiscal trends and forecasts.
  - Governor Warner's Proposed Budget for 2006 and the 2006-2008 Biennium, A Briefing for the Senate Finance Committee, the House Appropriations Committee, and the House Finance Committee (Draft Copy), 2005 Dec 15. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed Budget for 2008 and the 2008-2010 Biennium, A Briefing for the Senate Finance Committee, the House Appropriations Committee, and the House Finance Committee, 2007 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed Budget for 2008 and the 2008-2010 Biennium, A Briefing for the Senate Finance Committee, the House Appropriations Committee, and the House Finance Committee (with Richard Brown's notes and supporting documents), 2007 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2008, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2008 Aug 18. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed Amendments to the 2008-2010 Biennial Budget, A Briefing for the Joint Meeting of the Senate Finance Committee, House Appropriations Committee, and the House Finance Committee, by Daniel Timberlake, Director, Virginia Department of Planning and Budget, 2008 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed Amendments to the 2008-2010 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2008 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed Amendments to the 2008-2010 Biennial Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Halifax Chamber of Commerce, 2009 Jan 15. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2009, The Interim Economic Forecast for Fiscal Years 2010 through 2012, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2009 Aug 19. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Governor Kaine's Proposed 2010-2012 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2009 Dec 18. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 2010 Session, Budget Overview, Amendments to FY 2008-10 Budget; Proposed FY 2010-2012 Budget, 2010 Jan 14. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2010, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees (1 of 2), 2010 Aug 19. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2010, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees (2 of 2), 2010 Aug 19. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed Amendments to the 2010-2012 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees (1 of 3), 2010 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed Amendments to the 2010-2012 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees (2 of 3), 2010 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed Amendments to the 2010-2012 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees (3 of 3), 2010 Dec 17. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Overview of Governor McDonnell's Proposed Amendments to the 2010-2012 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Halifax County Chamber of Commerce, 2011 Jan 20. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2011, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2011 Aug 18. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed 2012-2014 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2011 Dec 19. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2012, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2012 Aug 15. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed Amendments to the 2012-2014 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2012 Dec 17. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2013, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2013 Aug 19. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed 2014-2016 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2013 Dec 16. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2014, The Interim Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast for Fiscal Years 2015 through 2016, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2014 Aug 15. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed Amendments to the 2014-2016 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2014 Dec 17. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2016, The Interim Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast for Fiscal Years 2017 through 2018, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Appropriations, and House Finance Committees, 2016 Aug 26. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed Amendments to the 2016-2018 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Appropriations Committees, 2016 Dec 16. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Briefing for Rating Agencies, Revenue Update and Governor's Budget Actions, 2017 Jan. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Review of General Fund Revenues and the Virginia Economy for Fiscal Year 2017, A Presentation to the Senate Finance, House Finance, and House Finance Committees, 2017 Aug 21. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed 2018-2020 Budget, Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast, A Briefing for the Senate Finance, House Appropriations and House Finance Committees, 2017 Dec 18. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2016 May. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2016 June. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2016 Sept. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2016 Oct. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2017 Jan. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2017 Feb. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Economic and Revenue Update, A Briefing for the Money Committees, 2017 Sept. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Series V. Planning and Budget Files, 2004-2006; 2012-2017., Extent: 13 boxes (9.21 cu. ft.). (Box 13-22; 28-30)
  Series V. Planning and Budget Files, 2004-2006; 2012-2017, created and maintained by Secretary of Finance Ric Brown, during multiple gubernatorial administrations, is housed in 13 boxes. This series documents the interactions between the Office of the Secretary of Finance and the Governor's staff, state agencies, and the Department of Planning and Budget regarding the development and modification of the Commonwealth's budget. This series may include, but is not limited to: incoming and outgoing correspondence, email, budget reports, budget amendments, capital outlay, notes and supporting documentation. This series appears to be in loose chronological order by legislative session. Capitol Outlay records are in loose reverse chronological order. While some records were foldered, none of them were labeled. Subjects include the state budget, state agency budget reduction plans, Medicaid expansion, legislation, revenue forecasts, and the Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates.
  - Governor McDonnell's Proposed Executive Amendments to the Introduced Budget (HB1500/SB800), 2013 Jan 14. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2013 May-Aug. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2013 Aug. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 2014 Legislative Proposals, 2013 Sept. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2013 Oct. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2013 Nov. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2013 Nov. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Capital Outlay, 2013-2014. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 2014 Regular Session, 2014 Jan. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 2014 Regular Session and Special Session I (1 of 2), 2014 Jan-Mar. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 2014 Regular Session and Special Session I (2 of 2), 2014 Jan-Mar. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2014 Special Session I, 2014 Mar. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2014 Special Session I, 2014 Mar. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2014 Special Session I (1 of 3), 2014 Mar-June. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2014 Special Session I (2 of 3), 2014 Mar-June. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2014 Special Session I (3 of 3), 2014 Mar-June. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2014 Special Session I (1 of 2), 2014 June. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2014 Special Session I (2 of 2), 2014 June. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 2014 Aug 1. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Joint Meeting of the Senate Finance, House Appropriations and House Finance Committees (1 of 2), 2014 Aug 15. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Joint Meeting of the Senate Finance, House Appropriations and House Finance Committees (2 of 2), 2014 Aug 15. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2014 Special Session I, 2014 Aug-Oct. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Medicaid Expansion, 2014 Apr-Oct. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Budget Reduction Plans for FY 2015, 2014 Aug; Oct. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2014 Special Session I, 2014 Aug-Sept. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2014 Oct. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2014 Oct-Nov. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2014 Nov. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2014 Nov-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2014 Dec. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 2015 Legislative Proposals, 2014 Sept. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 2015 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2015 Jan-Apr. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 2015 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2015 Jan-Apr. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 2015 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2015 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2015 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2015 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2015 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2015 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2015 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2015 Feb. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2015 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2015 Jan-Feb. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2015 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2015 Jan-Feb. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2015 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2015 Feb-Mar. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2015 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2015 Feb-Mar. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Mar. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 3), 2015 Mar-May. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 3), 2015 Mar-May. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 3), 2015 Mar-May. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Apr. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Hancock Geriatric Treatment Center (HGTC) Closure, 2015 June-Sept. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Medicaid Expansion, 2015 July-Oct. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Capital Outlay Budget, 2015 Oct. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Aug-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Sept-Dec. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 July-Aug. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Aug. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Sept-Nov. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Sept-Nov. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Oct-Nov. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Oct-Nov. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2015 Nov-Dec. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Finance Legislation (1 of 2), 2015 Dec-2016 Feb. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Finance Legislation (2 of 2), 2015 Dec-2016 Feb. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - General Fund Budget Spreadsheet, FY2017 and FY2018, 2017 Feb. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed 2016-2018 Budget, 2015 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed 2016-2018 Budget, 2015 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Governor McAuliffe's Proposed 2016-2018 Budget, 2015 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 2016-2018 Budget Roll Out, 2015 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 2016-2018 Budget Roll Out, 2015 Dec. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 2016 Regular Session, Economic Development, 2016 Jan-Feb. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 2016 Regular Session (1 of 5), 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 2016 Regular Session (2 of 5), 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - 2016 Regular Session (3 of 5), 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 2016 Regular Session (4 of 5), 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 2016 Regular Session (5 of 5), 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 2016 Regular Session, 2016 Feb. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 2016 Regular Session (1 of 2), 2016 Feb-Mar. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 2016 Regular Session (2 of 2), 2016 Feb-Mar. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Side by Side Comparison of HB/SB 29 and 30 Budget Actions (Conference Report Version) (1 of 2), 2016 Mar 15. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Side by Side Comparison of HB/SB 29 and 30 Budget Actions (Conference Report Version) (2 of 2), 2016 Mar 15. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 2016 Regular Session (1 of 4), 2016 Mar-Apr. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 2016 Regular Session (1 of 4), 2016 Mar-Apr. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - 2016 Regular Session (3 of 4), 2016 Mar-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 2016 Regular Session (4 of 4), 2016 Mar-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - 2016 Regular Session, 2016 Mar-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 2016 Veto Session, 2016 Apr. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Executive Amendments to the Budget, 2016 Session (1 of 2), 2015 Dec-2016 Mar. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Executive Amendments to the Budget, 2016 Session (2 of 2), 2015 Dec-2016 Mar. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bonds (1 of 3), 2016 Feb-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bonds (2 of 3), 2016 Feb-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Bonds (2 of 3), 2016 Feb-Apr. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2016 Apr-June. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 2016 Year End Close, 2016 June. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2016 June-July. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 3), 2016 May-Aug. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 3), 2016 May-Aug. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 3), 2016 May-Aug. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 5), 2016 Nov-Dec. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 5), 2016 Nov. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 5), 2016 Oct-Nov. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (4 of 5), 2016 Aug-Oct. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (5 of 5), 2016 Aug-Sept. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Budget Issues (Medicaid Expansion), 2016 Oct-Nov. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 4), 2016 July-Oct. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 4), 2016 July-Oct. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 4), 2016 July-Oct. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (4 of 4), 2016 July-Oct. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 4), 2016 July-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 4), 2016 July-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 4), 2016 July-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (4 of 4), 2016 July-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development, 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 2), 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 2), 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 3), 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 3), 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 3), 2016 Aug-Nov. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Joint Advisory Board of Economists Meeting, 2016 Nov 9. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (1 of 4), 2016 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (2 of 4), 2016 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (3 of 4), 2016 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Revenue Forecast and Budget Development (4 of 4), 2016 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - News stories on national economic conditions, 2016 Aug-Oct. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 2017 Regular Session, 2017 Jan-Feb. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 2017 Regular Session (1 of 3), 2017 Feb 5. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 2017 Regular Session (2 of 3), 2017 Feb 5. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 2017 Regular Session (3 of 3) 2017 Feb 7. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 2017 Regular Session, 2017 Feb. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 2017 Regular Session, 2017 Feb-Mar. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Bill Review, 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Budget Actions and Amendments (1 of 2), 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Budget Actions and Amendments (2 of 2), 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Budget Amendments, HB1500 (1 of 3), 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Budget Amendments, HB1500 (2 of 3), 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Budget Amendments, HB1500 (3 of 3), 2017 Mar. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Federal Budget Information, 2006; 2012; 2017. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Line of Duty Legislation, 2012; 2014-2016. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA), 2016-2017. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Revenue Information and Money Committee Presentations, 2014-2016. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA), VITA - Northrop Grumman Mediation/Settlement [RESTRICTED], 2017 Mar-Apr. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Capital Outlay, 2017 Apr-2016 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Capital Outlay, 2016 Sept-July. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Capital Outlay, 2016 July. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Capital Outlay, 2016 July. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Capital Outlay, 2016 June. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Capital Outlay, 2016 Jan-2015 Nov. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Capital Outlay, 2015 Oct-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Capital Outlay, 2015 Aug-May. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Capital Outlay, 2015 Apr-Jan. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Capital Outlay, 2014. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Capital Outlay, 2013. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Capital Outlay, Reference Documents, 2004-2005. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Series VI. Public Relations-Presentations, 2008; 2010; 2013-2014; 2017., Extent: 2 boxes (0.53 cu. ft.). (Box 24-25)
  Series VI. Public Relations-Presentations, 2008; 2010; 2013-2014; 2017, created and maintained by Secretary of Finance Ric Brown, during multiple gubernatorial administrations, is housed in two boxes. This series documents presentations made by the Secretary of Finance not covered in other series.
  - Economic, Revenue, and Budget Status Report for Virginia, A Presentation to the Virginia Municipal League (1 of 2), 2008 Sept 18. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Economic, Revenue, and Budget Status Report for Virginia, A Presentation to the Virginia Municipal League (2 of 2), 2008 Sept 18. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Core Services and Trends Affecting Intergovernmental Relations, Presentation to Governor McDonnell's Reform and Restructuring Commission, 2010 July 14. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - ABC Privatization and State Revenue, 2010 Sept 8. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Presentation to House Appropriations Committee, 2013 Nov 20. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Meeting with the Virginia Congressional Delegation (1 of 2), 2014 Apr 9. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Meeting with the Virginia Congressional Delegation (2 of 2), 2014 Apr 9. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Southside Cabinet Trip, 2014 July 28-29. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Tax 2017 Amnesty Program, 2017 Aug 9. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Matters Do Matter! - 2017 Governor's Transportation Conference, 2017 Oct 26. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Financial Considerations and Issues, Presented to Local Government Policy Council, 2017 Oct 31. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Overview of the HIS Markit Virginia Revenue Forecasting Review, 2017 Nov 14. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Series VII. Special Projects and Studies, 2012; 2014; 2016-2017., Extent: 2 boxes (1.35 cu. ft.). (Box 26-27)
  Series VI. Public Relations-Presentations, 2008; 2010; 2013-2014; 2017, created and maintained by Secretary of Finance Ric Brown, during the gubernatorial administrations of Robert McDonnell and Terry McAuliffe, is housed in two boxes. This series documents the office's interaction with and oversight of various projects and studies. The four projects and studies for the Secretary of Finance were: Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, Amazon (Retail Sales and Use Tax) Washington Redskins (now Washington Commanders) (financial incentives to move their practice facility to Richmond), Petersburg financial crisis, and Capital Outlay.
  The City of Petersburg had a major financial crisis in 2016. Tax collections were below 60 percent due to the closing of a pharmaceutical plant and the move of Brown and Williamson's corporate headquarters to Georgia. Petersburg City Council hired the DC based Robert Bobb Group to help with the city's finances. The Bobb Group worked with Secretary of Finance Ric Brown to secure needed funding for the city to pay its' bills. These records arranged loosely in chronological order document the actions taken by the secretary to stabilize Petersburg's finances in 2016 and 2017.
  - Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments (1 of 2), 2014 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments (2 of 2), 2014 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Amazon (Retail Sales and Use Tax), 2012 Jan-Feb. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Washington Redskins, 2012 Feb-Mar. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Washington Redskins, 2012 June. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Petersburg, 2016 June-July. (Box 26, Folder 6)